[Fragments of Truth]
[Episode 16]
Hello.
The license plate is fake.
Based on the marks at the scene,
my preliminary assessment is
that the driver may have been fatigued.
I'll ask the Traffic Accident Unit
to take another look tomorrow.
Okay.
Thanks for your help.
We're colleagues.
Don't mention it.
Sis!
Xiaowei.
Your sister just had a fright.
She's also had a little to drink.
Give her some yogurt when you get home,
and some tomato juice.
She'll be fine.
Uh...
Sorry to trouble you.
I apologize on my sister's behalf.
It's fine.
Something may be troubling your sister.
When you get home,
try to talk her through it.
Contact me anytime if anything happens.
Okay.
Go on.
Come on, Sis.
I've got her.
All right.
You should head home.
Be careful on the way.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Hey.
You nearly got into a car accident
just to buy a girl some water.
I was just careless.
That girl must mean a lot to you.
You've been like this since childhood,
always getting bumps and cuts.
Whenever I asked what happened,
you'd call scars a badge of manhood.
You're not real.
Ignoring me again?
You last ignored me
when you were in seventh grade.
One morning, you suddenly said
you wanted to quit school
and go earn money.
So I beat you.
You cried.
So did I.
Mom and Dad died when we were young.
We'd suffered so much.
If you even dropped out of school,
we'd suffer forever.
I don't care.
I just want you back.
I never imagined
the first time I hit you
would also be the last time I saw you.
Where are you?
[Missing Girl Files]
Sorry, boss.
Useless!
Is killing someone that hard?
He reacted too quickly.
I had no chance.
I promise it won't happen again.
Again?
You think there'll be another chance?
Do you take the police for fools?
Get ready.
Take everything you can.
Yes.
Uncle He,
I have evidence of Sun Jiahao's crimes.
I'm on my way to his company now.
Send a team to back me up right away.
Don't do anything rash.
Wait for our backup.
Okay.
All right.
See you in a bit.
Hurry!
Come out!
Get in the car!
Hurry!
Quick!
After her!
Run!
Keep running!
Stop!
Police!
Put it down!
Captain Ren.
I'm in the basement parking garage
at Luoda Biotech.
Get over here!
Are you okay?
Backup will be there any second.
Stay safe.
Whatever you do, don't...
Help me!
Sis...
Officer Han.
We meet again.
Sun Jiahao.
You're under arrest.
I didn't expect you to be so brave,
Officer.
You walked right into my hands.
Don't kill him.
Nobody move!
Police!
Get down!
Hands on your head!
Han Ning!
Call an ambulance!
♪I stand in a fire-tempered jungle♪
♪Withered leaves fall
as my strength runs dry♪
♪Dust swirls as I clench my fists♪
♪I strategize, my faith my armor♪
♪My defiance spills onto concrete♪
♪Even thick fog can't hide
my clear gaze♪
♪Let neon turn to thorns♪
♪Flying low as the stars shift and turn♪
♪Escape the maze,
transcend the challenge♪
♪The meter starts, breaking the silence♪
♪A beam cuts through
a crack in the wall♪
♪This rhythm and noise
echo through the streets♪
♪Don't be afraid. No one will answer♪
♪Why is that child crying?♪
♪The shrinking scar on my arm♪
♪Means I've grown up♪
♪You can trust me when I say that♪
♪The wound still aches♪
♪Like a biting winter♪
♪But a spark still glows♪
[Copyright in this complete short drama]
[Jointly owned by Beijing Hualu New
Media Information Technology Co., Ltd.]
[and Youku Information Technology
(Beijing) Co., Ltd.]
[Youku Information Technology (Beijing)
Co., Ltd. ("YOUKU") holds the]
[exclusive worldwide rights to online
distribution and broadcasting.]